question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
        "category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
